

Ben Chudyk

Creative Designer

About Me

I like to create things. I am either doing that through music, design or DIY projects. I also like to get things done. The best part about working with a client is seeing the final project launched and see how people are use it. I approach all my design with people with research and logic behind my decisions.



6967 179a Street Surrey, BC

778-241-8969

benchudyk.github.io ben.chudyk@gmail.com



Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign and SketchUP

HTML/CSS

Boostrap, Less, Sass, Wordpress, Woocommerce, Git, Jekyll



Work Experience

Graphic Designer

Radial Engineering

2014 - Present

Radial is a growing company and I am apart of a small marketing team that manages several brands. I work on projects that includ print, packaging, product photography, web design and online marketing initiatives.

Graphic Designer

Apple Security

2014 - 2015

I worked directly with the owner to implement a new wordpress site that used a child theme for custom styling. I also created promotional materials and helped with preparing bids for government contracts.

IT Support, Web Admin

Pacific Academy

2011-2014

Updated content and managed student web portals. Other duties included assisting teachers for general tech support, sound and lighting for events in main auditorium and other design projects around the school.

Graphic Designer

Fastsigns

2009-2011

Worked with customers from start to finish on their projects. Managed all large format printing and post production. Hands on work was required to have a completed product that was to the clients standards. I gained experience with vinyl application, vehicle wraps and banners.



Education

BCIT

2007-2009

Media Techniques and Marketing Communication

Pacific Academy

2005

High School Diploma